Jobs With Justice records 6369
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jobs With Justice records
1980-2019
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6369
56 cubic feet.
8332143
Box 1
Mapcase folder 1
Box 2
Mapcase folder 2
Box 3
Box 4
Box 5
Box 6
Box 7
Box 8
Box 9
Box 10
Box 11
Box 12
Box 13
Box 14
Box 15
Box 16
Box 17
Box 18
Box 19
Box 20
Box 21
Box 22
Box 23
Box 24
Box 25
Box 26
Box 27
Box 28
Box 29
Box 29A
Box 30
Box 31
Box 32
Box 33
Box 34
Box 35
Box 36
Box 37
Box 38
Box 39
Box 40
Box 41
Box 42
Box 43
Box 44
Box 45
Box 46
Box 47
Box 48
Box 49
Box 50
Box 51
Box 52
Box 53
Box 54
Box 55
Box 56
Scope and Contents
The Jobs With Justice records, 1980-2019, document the organization at the national and local levels and includes records of campaigns, newsletters, finances, and documentation of major projects including the Student Labor Action Project (SLAP), American Rights at Work (ARAW), and Workers Rights Boards (WRB). The collection also includes documentation of various events including annual JWJ member meetings, board meetings, the annual National Day of Action, and the annual SLAP Student Labor Day of Action and Week of Action. Other highlights of the collection include records of national campaigns in Series I, which includes material on health care reform and on campaigns against the FTAA, Verizon, and Wal-Mart, as well as extensive records of regional coalitions arranged by region and state in Series II.
Biographical / Historical
Jobs With Justice (JWJ) is a non-profit workers' advocacy organization based in Washington, D.C. Marking its beginning with a convening in Miami in 1987, JWJ started with members pledging to support others' fights for economic justice, as well as their own. Jobs With Justice organizes across community lines, working with community, student, faith, and organized labor groups. Significant JWJ campaigns include the Justice for Janitors (1985), Justice at Verizon (1989), and Justice at Smithfield (2008) campaigns. In 2012 Jobs With Justice announced a merger with American Rights at Work, another U.S. union advocate organization.[2] Jobs With Justice is based in Washington, D.C., and is led by Executive Director Erica Smiley. As of 2022, Jobs With Justice coalitions existed in over 30 cities or states in all regions of the country, and members now pledge to "stand up for our rights as working people to a decent standard of living; support the rights of all workers to organize and bargain collectively; fight for secure family-wage jobs in the face of corporate attacks on working people and our communities; organize the unorganized to take aggressive action to secure a better economic future for all of us; and mobilize those already organized to join the fight for Jobs With justice."
8332143
- Series I. National Jobs With Justice
  - Steering Committee Meeting, 1987-08 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Airline Workers, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Early Papers, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Jobs with Justice, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jobs with Justice History, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Jobs with Justice Information, 1987-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Labor Day, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jobs with Justice Success Stories, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Early Papers, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Steering Committee, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
  - Jobs with Justice - Video, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Jobs with Justice - Video, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Presidents Council Meetings, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Campaign for New Priorities, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Key and Steering Committee Mailings, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Coordinating Committee Meetings, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Campaign for New Priorities, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - New Priorities Campaign, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24-25)
  - New Priorities Campaign, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Campaign for New Priorities, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27-28)
  - Retreat Meeting, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Jobs with Justice Presentations, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Coordinating Meeting, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Presidents Council Meetings, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Washington State Planning Retreat, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Retreat Meetings, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Jobs with Justice Proposed Calendar of Meetings, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - President's Council Meeting, 1994-01-11 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - President's Council Meeting, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Presidents Council Meeting, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Presidents Council Meeting, 1994-01 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Steering Committee Mailing, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Steering Committee Mailings, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - President's Council Meeting, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
  - Presidents Council Meeting, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Jobs with Justice Structure, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Jobs with Justice Event and Media Reports, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - National Day of Action for "Bill of Rights for Working People", 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Oregon Planning Example, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Jobs with Justice Retreat, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Jobs with Justice AFL-CIO Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Worker Information/Interviews, 1996-06 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Washington State Retreat, 1996-11 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Presidents Council Meeting, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Key List Mailings, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Meeting-Presidents Council, 1996-02-28 (Box 8, Folder 29-30)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Stop-Corporate Greed, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Solidarity Request, Jobs with Justice Annual Meeting Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous, 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Staff Report, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Administrative Committee, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Event Report Forms, Jobs with Justice, 1997-11-26 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Presidents Council, 1997-09 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Steering Committee Mailings, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - National Steering Committee Meeting, 1997-07-14 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Old National Steering Committee Stuff, 1999-07 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Membership-Based Organizations vs. The Mobile Organizer Model, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Planning Committee, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
  - Snapshots/Surveys, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Planning Committee, 1997-07 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Planning Committee Meeting, 1997-07-12-1997-07-14 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Planning Resources, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - President Council, 1998-01-29 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Planning Committee, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Planning Committee Meeting, 1998-07-18-1998-07-20 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Planning Committee Meeting Food and Logistics, 1998-07 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Planning Committee Meeting, 1998-07 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Planning Committee Logistics, 1998-12 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Planning Committee Materials, 1998-12 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Planning Committee, 1998-12 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Jobs with Justice History, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Presidents Council, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Presidents Council Mailing, 1998-02 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Steering Committee, 1998-12 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Steering Committee, 1998-09 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Steering Committee, 1998-07 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Steering Committee Mailing, 1998-04 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Steering Committee, 1998-02 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Jobs with Justice - Steering Committee Meeting, 1999-11-05 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Steering Committee Attendance, 1999-04 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Steering Committee, 1999-04 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Presidents Council Meeting, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Presidents Council Mailing, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 27-28)
  - President's Council Packets, 1999-04 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Planning Committee Materials, 1999-04 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Planning Committee Various Documents, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Planning Committee, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Planning Committee Meeting, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Planning Committee Materials, 1999-11 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Jobs with Justice Committee Meeting, 1999-11-05-1999-11-07 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Planning Committee, 1999-11-05-1999-11-07 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - B.B. King Blues Festival, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Billy Bragg, 1999-08 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Concert Tour, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Communications Survey, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Planning Committee, 2000-06 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Union Tracking History, 2001-02 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Planning Committee, 2000-06-08-2000-06-09 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Planning Committee, 2000-12 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Cleveland Planning Retreat, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Planning Committee Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes floppy disk.
  - Jobs with Justice Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Jobs with Justice Planning Committee and Sustainable Growth Initiative Documents, 2000-12 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Steering Committee, 2000-09 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Jobs with Justice Personnel Policy, 2000-2002 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Grinch Parties, 2000-2004 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Strategic Planning Process Materials, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - National Allowance for Fair Employment, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Jobs with Justice Strategy Meetings (Region-Specific), 2001 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Jobs with Justice 501C3 Proof, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Strategic Growth Initiative, Workers Rights Board, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Jobs with Justice Field Team, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Planning Committee, 2001-06 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Planning Committee, 2001-06-03-2001-06-04 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Local Coalition Planning Guide, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Planning Committee, 2001-12 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Sample Materials, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Jobs with Justice - Application and Chartering, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Staff Meeting, 2002-04-19 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Policy, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Criteria for Selecting Campaigns, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - 501C3, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Recent Staff Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - NEA Expo, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Jobs with Justice (DC and National), 2003 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Staff Meeting, 2003-03-05 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Staff Meeting, 2003-05-07 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Jobs with Justice National Strategic Plan, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Planning Committee, 2005-12-10 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Work Plans, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Field Team, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Staff Meetings, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 37-38)
  - Transition Guide for Press Organizer, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Field Team - Anti-Racism and Oppression, 2000-12-03 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Staff Meetings, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Strategic Planning, 2008-2009 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Fair Hours National Strategy Meeting, 2016-12-05 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Transit Equity Day, 2019 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Jobs with Justice Affiliation Agreement, undated (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Annual Meetings
    - Annual Meeting Denver Expenses, 1991-03 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting Denver Handouts, 1991-03 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting Denver, 1991-03 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting Austin Expenses, 1992-02 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting Austin, 1992-02 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting Pittsburgh, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting Pittsburgh Rooming Lists/Expenses, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Annul Meeting Pittsburgh Handouts/Slide Show, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting Atlanta Handouts, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
    - Annual Meeting Atlanta, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting Cleveland, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Logistics, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Jobs With Justice Annual Report, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Planning Committee - Seattle Meeting, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Workshops, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Conference Evaluation, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - HUB, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting Seattle Washington, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meetings - Years Past, 1996-2000 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Seattle Annual Meeting, 1996-06 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Seattle Annual Meeting Room + Catering, 1996-06 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - JWJ 10th Anniversary Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Workshops - Chicago Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Annual Meeting Registration, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Agenda - '97 Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Meeting Rooms AV etc.. - '97 Chicago Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Ramada ALPHA Lists - '97 Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - JWJ 10th Anniversary Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - JWJ 10th Anniversary Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Annual Meeting Adbook, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Speaker Talking Points - '97 Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - JWJ 10th Anniversary Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Conference Book, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - National Staff Report, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Religious Labor Pre-Con, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting Agendas, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Rel. - Labor Pre-Con, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Annual Meeting Interfaith Service Excerpts, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Annual Meeting $$, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Annual Meeting Recruitment, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Religion Labor Pre-Conference, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Annual Meeting Schedule, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Speaker Invites, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Conference Follow-Up - Originals, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Pre-Registration Mailing, 1999-02-09 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Dartmouth JWJ, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Annual Meeting Flyer, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Jobs with Justice Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Pride @ Work Preconference, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Recruitment Ann Meeting, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Annual Meeting Recruitment, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Annual Meeting 2000 Misc. (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Annual Meeting Workshops, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting Report, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Workers' Rights Board - Annual Meeting - Hearing, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting Program, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting Ideas, Comments, Etc., 2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting Debrief, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting Recruitment, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting Program, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting Flyer, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Cleveland Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - JWJ 2001 Annual Meeting w/ SLAP (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
    - Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting, 2001-09-06-2001-09-09 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Annual Meeting - Cleveland, Ohio, 2001-09-06-2001-09-09 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting 4-Pager Brochure, 2001-09 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Friday Night Banquet, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Annual Meeting Report, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting Thanks, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting Brochures, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
    - Annual Meeting Planning, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Conference Agenda, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting Debrief, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meeting Prep, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Annual Meeting Thanks, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Annual Meeting Recruitment, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting Brochures, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Annual Meeting Agenda Doc, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - JWJ Annual Meeting Agenda (including SLAP), 2003 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Annual Meeting Mailings, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Contacts Re: Planning Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Music/Art, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Annual Meeting Samples, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Miami #s, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Speakers - Workshop Invites and Contact Info, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Workshops Ann Meeting, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - JWJ Annual Meeting, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Annual Meeting Scholarships, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Interfaith Service, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting Brochure (Conference), 2003 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Jobs with Justice Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - AV Needs, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Meals, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Millennium, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Map of Hotels and Convention Center, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - America's Center - Agreement, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 40-41)
    - America Center - Emails, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - JWJ Comp'd Room List, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Pre-Conferences, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Clergy Session - Faith in Action, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - AM Lists, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Immigrant Rights Pre-Conference, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Strategy Session, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - General Sessions, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - AM Budget, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - SLAP, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Renaissance Hotel, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Volunteer Grid, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Recruitment/Org Rel, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Program, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting Pre-Conferences, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting Program Committee, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Registration Packet, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Tabling Agreements, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Retreat + Debrief, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting Planning, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
    - America's Center, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Annotated Agenda, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Logistics, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Facilities, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - AV, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Childcare, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Translation + Doc, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meeting Recruitment and Money Debrief - Midwest, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting Debrief, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Faith in Action Registration, 2005-2006 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting: Case Study Originals Faith in Action, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Faith in Action Gathering, 2005-2006 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting Recruitment, 2005-2006 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Interfaith Service, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meeting - Jobs for Justice Breakfast, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting - On-site, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Annual Meeting Brochure (Conference), 2005 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Innovative Strategies, 2005-2006 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Economic Development Work for Communities Pre-Conference, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Annual Meeting Scholarships, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Annual Meeting - Debrief and Follow-Up, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Important Annual Meeting Documents, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Annual Meeting Outreach and Host Culture, 2005-05-2005-06 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Public Sector Pre-Conference, 2005-09-2005-10 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Staff Meeting, 2006-04 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - 15th Anniversary Awards Night, 2006-06-27 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Annual Awards Night Ceremony, 2007-10-25 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Annual Meeting - Providence, RI, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Jobs with Justice Annual Reports, 2010-2014 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - JWJ Education Fund Eleanor Roosevelt Human Rights Awards Celebration, 2015-06-24 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - National Conference, 2016 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - JWJ Education Fund Eleanor Roosevelt Human Rights Awards Celebration, 2018-06-20 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - National Campaigns
    - S 11 Reading, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - 9-11 Statements, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - 99% Spring, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Acorn Living Wage Campaign, 1995-1999 (Box 24, Folder 26-27)
    - America West Appeal, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Bail Out, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 48-49)
    - Boston Solidarity School, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Campaign For An America That Works, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Caring Across Generations - Care Cities, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Caring Across Generations Materials, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Center for Community Change, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Center for Community Change: Job Creation, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Citizens Trade Campaign, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - CLUE (Los Angeles), 1999-12 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Center for Economic and Policy Research, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Center for Economic Justice, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Coalition Collaborative, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - The Creative Coalition, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Delmarva Poultry Alliance, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Direct Action for Rights and Equality, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Driver's License Campaigns, 2005-03 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Dunlop Commission, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Employee Free Choice Act, 2005-2007 (Box 24, Folder 45-46)
    - Essential Action, Undated (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Fair Trade, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Faith Works, 1999-2002 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Fast Track, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Global Justice Strategy Session, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Free Time/Free People, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Frontlash, 1994-04 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - FTAA, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
    - FTAA Info, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 8-9)
    - FTAA, 1991-2001 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - FTAA, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - FTAA Local Actions - Alphabetical by State, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - FTAA, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Free Trade, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - FTAA, 2001-2003 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - FTAA and Immigrant Workers, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - FT/FTAA grant Agreement, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - FTAA Education, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - FTAA Materials, 2001-2003 (Box 25, Folder 19-20)
    - FTAA Educational, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - FTAA 4-Pager, 2003-11 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - FTAA 4-Pager, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - A21 FTAA Media, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Free Trade/FTAA Background, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Fuerza Unida - Levi Strauss Campaign, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - GATT, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 22)